<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="${descVersion}">
	<author>${author}</author>
	<version>${version}</version>
	<title>
		<en>Better Contracts</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[
This mod helps to improve the contract system, both in singleplayer and multyplayer.

- The maximum number and the amount of mission generated is now automatically adjusted to number of fields in map.
 
- You can now generate new missions through the "New Contracts" button and even clear them all on contracts management screen.

- Contracts are now sorted by type and field number to make it easier to find the one you desire.
 
- You can activate more than one contract at a time.
 
- The field-number indicator (on the mini-map) of the fields on which you will activate contracts, will start blinking to help you figure it out where you have to go.

Changelog ${version}:
- Added conflicts prevention with other mods
- Added contracts list sorting
- Added many new vehicle combos for contracts
- Improved contracts management
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
Dieser Mod hilft das Vertragssystem zu verbessern, sowohl im Einzelspieler und Multiplayer.

- Die maximale Anzahl und die Anzahl der generierten Missionen werden jetzt automatisch an die Anzahl der Felder in der Karte angepasst.
 
- Sie können jetzt über die Schaltfläche "Neue Verträge" neue Missionen generieren und diese sogar alle auf dem Vertragsverwaltungsbildschirm löschen.

- Verträge werden jetzt nach Typ und Feldnummer sortiert, um das Auffinden des gewünschten Vertrags zu erleichtern.
 
- Sie können mehr als einen Vertrag gleichzeitig aktivieren.
 
- Die Feldnummernanzeige (auf der Minikarte) der Felder, auf denen Sie Verträge aktivieren, beginnt zu blinken, um Ihnen den richtigen Weg zu zeigen.

Changelog ${version}:
- Konfliktverhütung mit anderen Mods hinzugefügt
- Sortierung der Vertragslisten hinzugefügt
- Es wurden viele neue Fahrzeugkombinationen für Verträge hinzugefügt
- Verbessertes Vertragsmanagement
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[
Ce mod aide à améliorer le système de contrat, à la fois en solo et multyplayer.

- Le nombre maximum et la quantité de missions générées sont désormais automatiquement ajustés au nombre de champs de la carte.
 
- Vous pouvez désormais générer de nouvelles missions via le bouton "Nouveaux contrats" et même les effacer toutes sur l'écran de gestion des contrats.

- Les contrats sont désormais triés par type et numéro de champ pour vous permettre de trouver plus facilement celui que vous désirez.
 
- Vous pouvez activer plusieurs contrats à la fois.
 
- L'indicateur de numéro de champ (sur la mini-carte) des champs sur lesquels vous allez activer les contrats, commencera à clignoter pour vous aider à déterminer où vous devez aller.

Changelog ${version}:
- Ajout de la prévention des conflits avec d'autres mods
- Ajout du tri de la liste des contrats
- Ajout de nombreux nouveaux combos de véhicules pour les contrats
- Amélioration de la gestion des contrats
]]>
		</fr>
	</description>
	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="lib/utility/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="lib/rmod/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="betterContractsNewEvent.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="betterContractsClearEvent.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="betterContracts.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="missionManagerFix.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>
	<l10n>
		<text name="bc_new_contracts">
			<en>New Contracts</en>
			<it>Nuovi Contratti</it>
			<de>Neue Verträge</de>
			<fr>Nouveaux Contrats</fr>
			<pl>Nowe kontrakty</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="bc_clear_contracts">
			<en>Clear Contracts</en>
			<it>Pulisci lista</it>
			<de>Klare Verträge</de>
			<fr>Clairs Contrats</fr>
			<pl>Wyczyść kontrakty</pl>
		</text>
	</l10n>
</modDesc>
