<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="${descVersion}">
	<author>${author}</author>
	<version>${version}</version>
	<title>
		<en>Better Contracts</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[
This mod helps to improve the contract system, both in singleplayer and multyplayer.

- The maximum number and the amount of mission generated has been increased to meet those who play on maps with many fields.
 
- You can now force the generation of new missions through the "Refresh" button on contract management screen.
 
- You can activate more than one contract at a time.
 
- The field-number indicator (on the mini-map) of the fields on which you will activate contracts, will start blinking to help you figure it out where you have to go.
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
Dieser Mod hilft, das Vertragssystem zu verbessern, sowohl in Einzelspieler und Multyplayer.

- Die maximale Anzahl und die Menge der generierten Mission wurde erhöht, um diejenigen zu treffen, die auf Karten mit vielen Feldern spielen.
 
- Sie können jetzt die Generierung neuer Missionen über die Schaltfläche "Aktualisieren" auf dem Bildschirm für die Vertragsverwaltung erzwingen.
 
- Sie können mehr als einen Vertrag gleichzeitig aktivieren.
 
- Die Feldnummernanzeige (auf der Mini-Karte) der Felder, auf denen Sie Verträge aktivieren werden, beginnt zu blinken, um herauszufinden, wohin Sie gehen müssen.
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[
Ce mod aide à améliorer le système de contrat, à la fois en solo et multyplayer.

- Le nombre maximal et la quantité de mission générée a été augmenté pour rencontrer ceux qui jouent sur des cartes avec de nombreux champs.
 
- Vous pouvez maintenant forcer la génération de nouvelles missions à travers le bouton « resho » sur l’écran de gestion des contrats.
 
- Vous pouvez activer plus d’un contrat à la fois.
 
- L’indicateur de numéro de champ (sur la mini-carte) des champs sur lesquels vous activerez les contrats, commencera à clignoter pour vous aider à comprendre où vous devez aller.
]]>
		</fr>
	</description>
	<iconFilename>icon_betterContracts.dds</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="betterContractsRefreshEvent.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="betterContracts.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>
	<l10n>
		<text name="refresh_contracts">
			<en>Refresh Contracts</en>
			<it>Aggiorna Contratti</it>
			<de>Verträge aktualisieren</de>
			<fr>Actualiser les contrats</fr>
		</text>
	</l10n>
</modDesc>
